RG 071:003, Department of Housing Planning Maps
Connecticut State Library
- Dept. of Community Affairs. Planning Maps, circa 1943-1980
  - Manchester (Box 6)
    - Parking inventory, 1960; Planning and renewal Associates; 24 x 49.5 in.; 1 inch = 100 feet (Box 6)
    - Parking acquisitions, 1970; Planning and renewal Associates; 24 x 49.5 in.; 1 inch = 100 feet (Box 6)
    - Future land use, 1980; Planning and renewal Associates; 24 x 49.5 in.; 1 inch = 100 feet (Box 6)
  - Mansfield (Box 6)
    - Existing topography and improvements, 1977 September; Flaherty Giavara Associates; 42.5 x 49.25 in.; 1 inch = 100 feet (Box 6)
    - Existing land use, 1977 September; Flaherty Giavara Associates; 42.5 x 49.25 in.; 1 inch = 100 feet (Box 6)
    - Borings and surficial geology, 1977 September; Flaherty Giavara Associates; 42.5 x 49.25 in.; 1 inch = 100 feet (Box 6)
    - Acquisition map, 1977 September; Flaherty Giavara Associates; 42.5 x 49.25 in.; 1 inch = 100 feet (Box 6)
    - Proposed land use and zoning, 1977 September; Flaherty Giavara Associates; 42.5 x 49.25 in.; 1 inch = 100 feet (Box 6)
    - Proposed streets and sanitary sewers, 1977 September; Flaherty Giavara Associates; 42.5 x 49.25 in.; 1 inch = 100 feet (Box 6)
    - Proposed storm drainage and water system, 1977 September; Flaherty Giavara Associates; 42.5 x 49.25 in.; 1 inch = 100 feet (Box 6)
    - Proposed electrical, telephone & gas service, 1977 September; Flaherty Giavara Associates; 42.5 x 49.25 in.; 1 inch = 100 feet (Box 6)
    - Disposition map, 1977 September; Flaherty Giavara Associates; 42.5 x 49.25 in.; 1 inch = 100 feet (Box 6)
    - Development plan, 1977 September; Flaherty Giavara Associates; 42.5 x 49.25 in.; 1 inch = 100 feet (Box 6)
    - Plan of development, 1970; Brown, Donald and Donald; 42 x 55.75 in.; 1 inch = 1000 feet (Box 6)
    - Plan of development, 1970; Brown, Donald and Donald; 42 x 55.75 in.; 1 inch = 1000 feet (Box 6)
  - Marlborough (Box 6)
    - Blish memorial park, 1967 June 9; Peter Abel; 62 x 35.5 in.; 1 inch = 50 feet (Box 6)
  - Meriden (Box 6)
    - Zoning map, 1959; Candeub and Fleissig Consultants; 73 x 33.5 in. (Box 6)
    - CDAP - Illustrative Pert Network, undated; 104 x 42 in. (Box 6)
  - Milford (Box 6)
    - Zoning map, 1962 August 1; 27 x 22 in.; 1 inch = 1600 feet (Box 6)
  - Monroe (Box 6)
    - Street index, undated; Brown, Donald and Donald; 20.5 x 25 in.; 1 inch = 2000 feet (Box 6)
  - New Canaan (Box 6)
    - Zoning map, 1950 March 6; Walter K. Goodhue, C.E.; 15 x 11 in. (Box 6)
  - New Hartford (Box 6)
    - Preliminary comprehensive plans, 1957 February 28; Yarwood & Block, Inc.; 42 x 33 in. (Box 6)
    - Regional base map, 1957 February 28; Yarwood & Block, Inc.; 42 x 33 in.; 1 inch = 2600 feet (Box 6)
      plan number: 16
    - Topography, 1957 February 28; Yarwood & Block, Inc.; 42 x 33 in.; 1 inch = 1200 feet (Box 6)
      plan number: 18
    - New hartford center - special study, 1957 February 28; Yarwood & Block, Inc.; 42 x 33 in.; 1 inch = 1000 feet (Box 6)
      plan number: 19
    - Regional topo, 1957 February 28; Yarwood & Block, Inc.; 42 x 33 in.; 1 inch = 2600 feet (Box 6)
      plan number: 21
    - Regional drainage, 1957 February 28; Yarwood & Block, Inc.; 42 x 33 in.; 1 inch = 2600 feet (Box 6)
      plan number: 22
    - Regional circulation, 1957 February 28; Yarwood & Block, Inc.; 42 x 33 in.; 1 inch = 2600 feet (Box 6)
      plan number: 24
    - Electric power lines, 1957 February 28; Yarwood & Block, Inc.; 42 x 33 in.; 1 inch = 2600 feet (Box 6)
      plan number: 25A
    - Public facilites, 1957 February 28; Yarwood & Block, Inc.; 42 x 33 in.; 1 inch = 2600 feet (Box 6)
      plan number: 26
    - Major thoroughfares, 1957 February 28; Yarwood & Block, Inc.; 42 x 33 in.; 1 inch = 2600 feet (Box 6)
      plan number: 27
    - Water courses, 1957 February 28; Yarwood & Block, Inc.; 42 x 33 in.; 1 inch = 2600 feet (Box 6)
      plan number: 29
    - Water supply, 1957 February 28; Yarwood & Block, Inc.; 42 x 33 in.; 1 inch = 2600 feet (Box 6)
      plan number: 29A
    - Flood plain map, 1957 February 28; Yarwood & Block, Inc.; 42 x 33 in.; 1 inch = 2600 feet (Box 6)
      plan number: 30
    - Slope map, 1957 February 28; Yarwood & Block, Inc.; 42 x 33 in.; 1 inch = 2600 feet (Box 6)
      plan number: 31
    - Population density, 1957 February 28; Yarwood & Block, Inc.; 42 x 33 in.; 1 inch = 2600 feet (Box 6)
      plan number: 32
    - Population centers, 1957 February 28; Yarwood & Block, Inc.; 42 x 33 in.; 1 inch = 2600 feet (Box 6)
      plan number: 32A
    - Population centers, 1957 February 28; Yarwood & Block, Inc.; 42 x 33 in.; 1 inch = 2600 feet (Box 6)
      plan number: 32B
    - Population growth, 1957 February 28; Yarwood & Block, Inc.; 42 x 33 in.; 1 inch = 2600 feet (Box 6)
      plan number: 33
    - Public facilities, 1957 February 28; Yarwood & Block, Inc.; 42 x 33 in.; 1 inch = 2600 feet (Box 6)
      plan number: 35
    - Proposed sewerage, 1957 February 28; Yarwood & Block, Inc.; 42 x 33 in.; 1 inch = 2600 feet (Box 6)
      plan number: 36B
    - Traffic flow, 1957 February 28; Yarwood & Block, Inc.; 42 x 33 in.; 1 inch = 2600 feet (Box 6)
      plan number: 37A
    - Major thoroughfares, 1957 February 28; Yarwood & Block, Inc.; 42 x 33 in.; 1 inch = 2600 feet (Box 6)
      plan number: 37B
    - Existing zoning, 1957 February 28; Yarwood & Block, Inc.; 42 x 33 in.; 1 inch = 2600 feet (Box 6)
      plan number: 42
    - Proposed zoning, 1957 February 28; Yarwood & Block, Inc.; 42 x 33 in.; 1 inch = 2600 feet (Box 6)
      plan number: 43
    - Zoning map, 1967 January; Brown, Donald and Donald; 23 x 17.5 in.; 1 inch = 2000 feet (Box 6)
    - Zoning map, 1967 January; Brown, Donald and Donald; 23 x 17.5 in.; 1 inch = 2000 feet (Box 6)
  - New Haven (Box 6)
    - 20 section maps that have been reduced from larger maps, 1963 January 1; City Plan Commission; 11 x 8.5 in. (Box 6)
  - Newington (Box 6)
    - Water distribution system, 1975; The Metropolitan District; 30.75 x 24.25 in.; 1 inch = 1000 feet (Box 6)
    - Sanitary sewer system, 1975; The Metropolitan District; 30.75 x 24.25 in.; 1 inch = 1000 feet (Box 6)
  - Newtown (Box 6)
    - Base map, undated; Flaherty Giavara Associates; 48 x 42.5 in.; 1 inch = 1200 feet (Box 6)
      plan number: Sheet 3 composite
  - North Haven (Box 6)
    - Zoning map, 1960 January 1; TPA; 23.75 x 17.75 in.; 1 inch = 1600 feet (Box 6)
  - Norwalk (Box 6)
    - Untitled, 1970 November 27; 43 x 25 in. (Box 6)
    - Community development plan outline, 1975 February 17; 58.5 x 36 in.; 1 inch = 400 feet (Box 6)
    - Housing assistance plan, 1975 March 1; 24 x 14.5 in.; 1 inch = .5 mile (Box 6)
  - Norwich (Box 6)
    - Zoning map Town consolidated district, 1976 August; 30 x 21 in.; 1 inch =1600 feet (Box 6)
    - Zoning map city consolidated district, 1976 June; 30 x 21 in.; 1 inch = 800 feet (Box 6)
    - Flood insurance rate map, 1978 June 15; U.S. Department of Housing; 26 x 37.5 in.; 1 inch = 1000 feet (Box 6)
    - Flood insurance rate map, 1978 June 15; U.S. Department of Housing; 26 x 37.5 in.; 1 inch = 1000 feet (Box 6)
  - Old Lyme (Box 6)
    - Building zone map, 1957 January 2; 18.5 x 17.5 in.; 1 inch = 2000 feet (Box 6)
    - Town roads, 1970 September; 17.5 x 19 in.; 2.5 inch = 1 mile (Box 6)
    - Town roads, 1970 September; 17.5 x 19 in.; 2.5 inch = 1 mile (Box 6)
  - Oxford (Box 6)
    - Community survey of Oxford, 1969 October (Box 6)
    - Recommendations for revisions to the Oxford zoning regulations, 1965 December; E. H. Lord-Wood Associates (Box 6)
    - Base map, 1964 September; E. H. Lord-Wood Associates; 63.5 x 42.25 in.; 1 inch = 1000 feet (Box 6)
    - Base map, 1964 September; E. H. Lord-Wood Associates; 63.5 x 42.25 in.; 1 inch = 1000 feet (Box 6)
    - Topography, 1964 September; E. H. Lord-Wood Associates; 63.5 x 42.25 in.; 1 inch = 1000 feet (Box 6)
    - Land classification map, 1964 September; E. H. Lord-Wood Associates; 63.5 x 42.25 in.; 1 inch = 1000 feet (Box 6)
    - Existing land use, 1964 September; E. H. Lord-Wood Associates; 63.5 x 42.25 in.; 1 inch = 1000 feet (Box 6)
    - Existing land use, 1964 September; E. H. Lord-Wood Associates; 63.5 x 42.25 in.; 1 inch = 1000 feet (Box 6)
    - Population distribution, 1964 September; E. H. Lord-Wood Associates; 63.5 x 42.25 in.; 1 inch = 1000 feet (Box 6)
    - Neighborhoods - planning - districts, 1964 September; E. H. Lord-Wood Associates; 63.5 x 42.25 in.; 1 inch = 1000 feet (Box 6)
      plan number: II-G
    - Zoning map, 1964 September; E. H. Lord-Wood Associates; 63.5 x 42.25 in.; 1 inch = 1000 feet (Box 6)
    - Comprehensive plan, 1965 September; E. H. Lord-Wood Associates; 63.5 x 42.25 in.; 1 inch = 1000 feet (Box 6)
    - Topography, 1965 September; E. H. Lord-Wood Associates; 63.5 x 42.25 in.; 1 inch = 1000 feet (Box 6)
  - Plainfield (Box 6)
    - Boring location plan, undated; 62 x 42.5 in.; 1 inch = 100 feet (Box 6)
      plan number: CEM # 2936
    - Proposed Roadway profile road "A", undated; CE Maguire, Inc.; 87.5 x 21.75 in. (Box 6)
    - Proposed Roadway profile road "B", undated; CE Maguire, Inc.; 87.5 x 21.75 in. (Box 6)
    - Proposed roadway profile Shepherd Hill Road, undated; CE Maguire, Inc.; 87.5 x 21.75 in. (Box 6)
    - Disposition map, 1977 September; CE Maguire, Inc.; 62 x 42.5 in.; 1 inch = 100 feet (Box 6)
    - Acquisition plan (A-2 survey), 1977 September 8; CE Maguire, Inc.; 22 x 36 in.; 1 inch = 200 feet (Box 6)
    - Proposed road ways and drainage, 1977 September; CE Maguire, Inc.; 62 x 42.5 in.; 1 inch = 100 feet (Box 6)
    - Sanitary sewer and water, 1977 September; CE Maguire, Inc.; 62 x 42.5 in.; 1 inch = 100 feet (Box 6)
    - Proposed land use and zoning, CE Maguire, Inc.; 32 x 24 in.; 1 inch = 200 feet (Box 6)
    - Existing topography and boundary map, 1977 September; CE Maguire, Inc.; 62 x 42.5 in.; 1 inch = 100 feet (Box 6)
  - Plymouth (Box 7)
    - Existing land use, 1959 July; S. Spielvogel and Associates; 52 x 36 in.; 1 inch = .5 mile (Box 7)
      701 project: Conn. P-11
    - Major traffic flow, 1959 July; S. Spielvogel and Associates; 52 x 36 in.; 1 inch = .5 mile (Box 7)
    - Topography, undated; S. Spielvogel and Associates; 52 x 36 in.; 1 inch = 800 feet (Box 7)
    - Soil charateristics, 1959 August; S. Spielvogel and Associates; 52 x 36 in.; 1 inch = 800 feet (Box 7)
    - Development characteristics, 1959 August; S. Spielvogel and Associates; 52 x 36 in.; 1 inch = 800 feet (Box 7)
    - Conditions of roads, 1959 August; S. Spielvogel and Associates; 52 x 36 in.; 1 inch = 800 feet (Box 7)
    - Building growth, 1959 August; S. Spielvogel and Associates; 52 x 36 in.; 1 inch = 800 feet (Box 7)
    - Existing utilities, 1959 August; S. Spielvogel and Associates; 52 x 36 in.; 1 inch = 800 feet (Box 7)
    - Public facilities, 1959 August; S. Spielvogel and Associates; 52 x 36 in.; 1 inch = 800 feet (Box 7)
    - Population growth distribution and density, 1959 August; S. Spielvogel and Associates; 52 x 36 in.; 1 inch = 800 feet (Box 7)
    - Major street plan, 1959 August; S. Spielvogel and Associates; 52 x 36 in.; 1 inch = 800 feet (Box 7)
    - Extension of public facilities, 1959 August; S. Spielvogel and Associates; 52 x 36 in.; 1 inch = 800 feet (Box 7)
  - Portland (Box 7)
    - Building zone map, 1957 January; Technical Planning Associates; 20.25 x 18 in.; 1 inch = 2000 feet (Box 7)
    - Existing land use, 1965 June 30; Technical Planning Associates; 38.5 x 36 in.; 1 inch = 1000 feet (Box 7)
      701 project: Conn. P-46
    - Conditions of buildability, 1965 June 30; Technical Planning Associates; 38.5 x 36 in.; 1 inch = 1000 feet (Box 7)
    - Population distribution and neighborhood growth, 1964 August; Technical Planning Associates; 38.5 x 36 in.; 1 inch = 1000 feet (Box 7)
    - Location and extent of blight, 1964 August; Technical Planning Associates; 38.5 x 36 in.; 1 inch = 1000 feet (Box 7)
    - Location and extent of blight, 1964 August; Technical Planning Associates; 38.5 x 36 in.; 1 inch = 1000 feet (Box 7)
    - Land use plan, 1965 September; Technical Planning Associates; 38.5 x 36 in.; 1 inch = 1000 feet (Box 7)
    - Residential densities plan, 1965 September; Technical Planning Associates; 38.5 x 36 in.; 1 inch = 1000 feet (Box 7)
    - Public facilities plan, 1965 September; Technical Planning Associates; 38.5 x 36 in.; 1 inch = 1000 feet (Box 7)
    - Building zone map, 1965 October; Technical Planning Associates; 38.5 x 36 in.; 1 inch = 1000 feet (Box 7)
    - Conditions of buildability, 1965 June 30; Technical Planning Associates; 38.5 x 36 in.; 1 inch = 1000 feet (Box 7)
    - Building zone map, 1965 October; Technical Planning Associates; 38.5 x 36 in.; 1 inch = 1000 feet (Box 7)
    - Circulation plan, 1965 September; Technical Planning Associates; 38.5 x 36 in.; 1 inch = 1000 feet (Box 7)
  - Somers (Box 7)
    - Industry and business map, 1948; 43 x 33 in.; 4 inch = 1 mile (Box 7)
  - Sprague (Box 7)
    - Base map & topography, undated; M.E.H. Rotival & Associates; 44 x 38.25 in.; 1 inch = 2400 feet (Box 7)
    - Baltic base map, undated; M.E.H. Rotival & Associates; 25.5 x 38 in.; 1 inch = 160 feet (Box 7)
    - Generialized land use, undated; M.E.H. Rotival & Associates; 43 x 36.25 in.; 1 inch = 2400 feet (Box 7)
    - Baltic land use, undated; M.E.H. Rotival & Associates; 16.5 x 21.25 in.; 1 inch = 320 feet (Box 7)
    - Problems - facts & diagnosis, undated; M.E.H. Rotival & Associates; 36 x 50.5 in.; 1 inch = 800 feet (Box 7)
    - Existing industry, undated; M.E.H. Rotival & Associates; 18 x 19.5 in.; 1 inch = 1600 feet (Box 7)
    - Existing social facilities, undated; M.E.H. Rotival & Associates; 18 x 19.5 in.; 1 inch = 1600 feet (Box 7)
    - Existing traffic volumes, undated; M.E.H. Rotival & Associates; 18 x 19.5 in.; 1 inch = 1600 feet (Box 7)
    - Existing and proposed roads, undated; M.E.H. Rotival & Associates; 36.25 x 41 in.; 1 inch = 800 feet (Box 7)
    - Directive plan for baltic, undated; M.E.H. Rotival & Associates; 22.75 x 32.5 in.; 1 inch = 350 feet (Box 7)
    - Social & public facilities plan, undated; M.E.H. Rotival & Associates; 18 x 19.5 in.; 1 inch = 1600 feet (Box 7)
  - Stafford (Box 7)
    - Peterson Memorial Park (3 small maps), undated (Box 7)
  - Stamford (Box 7)
    - Proposed zoning map, 1951 November 30; 54 x 26 in.; 1 inch = 1800 feet (Box 7)
    - Zoning map, 1961 December 15; Planning and Zoning Board of Stamford; 50 x 27 in.; 1 inch = 1800 feet (Box 7)
  - Stratford (Box 7)
    - Zoning map, 1956 October 1; Bureau of Engineering; 18 x 11 in.; 1 inch = 3000 feet (Box 7)
    - Zoning map, 1969 November 16; Planning and Zoning; 57.5 x 36 in.; 1 inch = 1000 feet (Box 7)
  - Suffield (Box 7)
    - Zoning map, undated; Technical Planning Associates; 15 x 15 in. (Box 7)
  - Thomaston (Box 7)
    - Town of Thomaston planning commission pamphlet, 1957 July (Box 7)
    - Regional Topography, 1956; Technical Planning Associates; 25 x 17.25 in.; 1 inch = 1 mile (Box 7)
      plan number: R- 1.1
    - Regional drainage, 1956; Technical Planning Associates; 25 x 17.25 in.; 1 inch = 1 mile (Box 7)
      plan number: R- 1.2
    - Population trends & projections, 1956; Technical Planning Associates; 25 x 17.25 in. (Box 7)
      plan number: R- 2.11 T- 2.11
    - Comparative growth, 1955; Technical Planning Associates; 25 x 17.25 in. (Box 7)
      plan number: R- 2.12
    - Regional traffic flow, 1955; Technical Planning Associates; 25 x 17.25 in.; 1 inch = 3 miles (Box 7)
      plan number: R- 4.12
    - Regional public finance, 1956; Technical Planning Associates; 25 x 17.25 in. (Box 7)
      plan number: R- 6.11
    - Regional public finance % change 1946-1956, Technical Planning Associates; 25 x 17.25 in. (Box 7)
      plan number: R- 6.12
    - Regional employment, 1955; Technical Planning Associates; 25 x 17.25 in. (Box 7)
      plan number: R- 6.21
    - Regional trends in manufacturing, 1955; Technical Planning Associates; 25 x 17.25 in. (Box 7)
      plan number: R- 6.22
    - Regional retail trade volume and sales per capita, 1955; Technical Planning Associates; 25 x 17.25 in. (Box 7)
      plan number: R- 6.23
    - Drainage areas, 1955; Technical Planning Associates; 25 x 17.25 in.; 1 inch = 1600 feet (Box 7)
      plan number: T- 1.2
    - Soil types, 1957; Technical Planning Associates; 25 x 17.25 in.; 1 inch = 1600 feet (Box 7)
      plan number: T- 1.4
    - Family data, 1955; Technical Planning Associates; 25 x 17.25 in. (Box 7)
      plan number: T- 2.21
    - Population characteristics, 1955; Technical Planning Associates; 25 x 17.25 in. (Box 7)
      plan number: T- 2.22
    - Population distribution, 1956 July; Technical Planning Associates; 25 x 17.25 in.; 1 inch = 1600 feet (Box 7)
      plan number: T- 2.23
    - Housing distribution, 1955 September; Technical Planning Associates; 25 x 17.25 in.; 1 inch = 1600 feet (Box 7)
      plan number: T- 3.21
    - Damaged structures, 1955 August 19; Technical Planning Associates; 25 x 17.25 in.; 1 inch = 1600 feet (Box 7)
      plan number: T- 3.22 T- 6.2
    - Public transportation and moptor vehicle registration, 1956; Technical Planning Associates; 25 x 17.25 in. (Box 7)
      plan number: T- 4.2 T-4.3
    - Existing parking facilities in central park, 1956 July; Technical Planning Associates; 25 x 17.25 in. (Box 7)
      plan number: T- 4.4
    - Existing arteries, 1956; Technical Planning Associates; 25 x 17.25 in.; 1 inch = 1600 feet (Box 7)
      plan number: T-4.11
    - Existing traffic flows, 1955; Technical Planning Associates; 25 x 17.25 in.; 1 inch = 1600 feet (Box 7)
      plan number: T- 4.12
    - Community facilities, 1956; Technical Planning Associates; 25 x 17.25 in.; 1 inch = 1600 feet (Box 7)
      plan number: T- 5.1 T- 5.2
    - Water utilities I, 1956; Technical Planning Associates; 25 x 17.25 in.; 1 inch = 400 feet (Box 7)
      plan number: T- 5.31
    - Proposed sewers utilities II, 1956; Technical Planning Associates; 25 x 17.25 in.; 1 inch = 400 feet (Box 7)
      plan number: T- 5.32
    - Gas utilities III, 1956; Technical Planning Associates; 25 x 17.25 in.; 1 inch = 400 feet (Box 7)
      plan number: T- 5.33
    - Town finances, 1956; Technical Planning Associates; 25 x 17.25 in. (Box 7)
      plan number: T- 6.1
    - Areas most suitable for development, 1955; Technical Planning Associates; 25 x 17.25 in.; 1 inch = 1600 feet (Box 7)
      plan number: T- 7.1
    - Areas most suitable for development- by soil type, 1955; Technical Planning Associates; 25 x 17.25 in.; 1 inch = 1600 feet (Box 7)
    - Neighborhood development & school location, Technical Planning Associates; 25 x 17.25 in.; 1 inch = 1600 feet (Box 7)
      plan number: T- 8.3 T-8.2
    - Proposed improvements in regional and local roads, Technical Planning Associates; 25 x 17.25 in.; 1 inch = 1600 feet (Box 7)
      plan number: T- 8.5
    - Plan of center, 1957; Technical Planning Associates; 25 x 17.25 in.; 1 inch = 400 feet (Box 7)
      plan number: T- 8.61
    - Plan of center, 1957; Technical Planning Associates; 25 x 17.25 in.; 1 inch = 400 feet (Box 7)
      plan number: T- 8.62
    - Preliminary zoning map, undated; Technical Planning Associates; 25 x 17.25 in.; 1 inch = 1600 feet (Box 7)
      plan number: T- 9
    - Zoning map, 1971 March; S. Spielvogel and Associates; 56 x 42 in. (Box 7)
      701 project: Conn. P-98
    - Major traffic volume, undated; S. Spielvogel and Associates; 56 x 42 in.; 1 inch = 2000 feet (Box 7)
    - Soil, undated; S. Spielvogel and Associates; 56 x 42 in.; 1 inch = 800 feet (Box 7)
    - Generalized existing land use, undated; S. Spielvogel and Associates; 56 x 42 in.; 1 inch = 800 feet (Box 7)
    - Development factors, undated; S. Spielvogel and Associates; 56 x 42 in.; 1 inch = 800 feet (Box 7)
    - Road classification and recent subdivision activity, undated; S. Spielvogel and Associates; 56 x 42 in.; 1 inch = 800 feet (Box 7)
    - Existing public utilities, undated; S. Spielvogel and Associates; 56 x 42 in.; 1 inch = 800 feet (Box 7)
    - Existing public facilities, undated; S. Spielvogel and Associates; 56 x 42 in.; 1 inch = 800 feet (Box 7)
    - Proposedland use, undated; S. Spielvogel and Associates; 56 x 42 in.; 1 inch = 800 feet (Box 7)
    - Neighborhood areas population growth - distribution and density, undated; S. Spielvogel and Associates; 56 x 42 in.; 1 inch = 800 feet (Box 7)
    - Major street plan, undated; S. Spielvogel and Associates; 56 x 42 in.; 1 inch = 800 feet (Box 7)
    - Extension of public facilities, undated; S. Spielvogel and Associates; 56 x 42 in.; 1 inch = 800 feet (Box 7)
    - Plan of development, undated; S. Spielvogel and Associates; 56 x 42 in.; 1 inch = 800 feet (Box 7)
  - Tolland (Box 7)
    - Base map, 1963 September; Stelling, Lord-Wood and Van Suetendael; 41.5 x 48 in.; 1 inch = 1000 feet (Box 7)
      701 project: Conn. P-36
    - Topographic base map, 1963 September; Stelling, Lord-Wood and Van Suetendael; 41.5 x 48 in.; 1 inch = 1000 feet (Box 7)
    - General soil map, 1963 September; Stelling, Lord-Wood and Van Suetendael; 41.5 x 48 in.; 1 inch = 1000 feet (Box 7)
      plan number: II-c
    - Existing land uses, 1963 September; Stelling, Lord-Wood and Van Suetendael; 41.5 x 48 in.; 1 inch = 1000 feet (Box 7)
    - Population distribution, 1963 September; Stelling, Lord-Wood and Van Suetendael; 41.5 x 48 in.; 1 inch = 1000 feet (Box 7)
    - Neighborhoods, 1963 September; Stelling, Lord-Wood and Van Suetendael; 41.5 x 48 in.; 1 inch = 1000 feet (Box 7)
      plan number: II-g
    - Comprehensive plan, 1964 July; Stelling, Lord-Wood and Van Suetendael; 41.5 x 48 in.; 1 inch = 1000 feet (Box 7)
  - Vernon (Box 7)
    - Street and traffic circulation plan, 1967 August; Raymond & May Associates; 32 x 28 in.; 1 inch = 1000 feet (Box 7)
    - Zoning map, 1967 August; Raymond & May Associates; 32 x 28 in.; 1 inch = 1000 feet (Box 7)
    - Sanitary sewers, 1967 August; Raymond & May Associates; 32 x 28 in.; 1 inch = 1000 feet (Box 7)
    - Land use plan, 1967 August; Raymond & May Associates; 32 x 28 in.; 1 inch = 1000 feet (Box 7)
    - Buildable land map, 1967 August; Raymond & May Associates; 32 x 28 in.; 1 inch = 1000 feet (Box 7)
    - Neighborhood delineations, 1967 August; Raymond & May Associates; 32 x 28 in.; 1 inch = 1000 feet (Box 7)
    - Storm drainage, 1967 August; Raymond & May Associates; 32 x 28 in.; 1 inch = 1000 feet (Box 7)
    - Community facilities plan, 1967 August; Raymond & May Associates; 32 x 28 in.; 1 inch = 1000 feet (Box 7)
    - Fire district, undated; Technical planning Associates; 32.5 x 29.5 in.; 1 inch = 1000 feet (Box 7)
    - Natural features, undated; Technical planning Associates; 32.5 x 29.5 in.; 1 inch = 1000 feet (Box 7)
    - Conditions of buildability of land, undated; Technical planning Associates; 32.5 x 29.5 in.; 1 inch = 1000 feet (Box 7)
      plan number: II-D,E
    - Circulation plan, undated; Technical planning Associates; 32.5 x 29.5 in.; 1 inch = 1000 feet (Box 7)
    - Zoning map, 1963 March 8; Technical planning Associates; 15 x 13 in.; 1 inch = 400 feet (Box 7)
      plan number: I
    - Zoning map, 1963 March 8; Technical planning Associates; 15 x 13 in.; 1 inch = 400 feet (Box 7)
      plan number: II
    - Zoning map, 1963 March 8; Technical planning Associates; 15 x 13 in.; 1 inch = 400 feet (Box 7)
      plan number: III
    - Zoning map, 1963 March 8; Technical planning Associates; 15 x 13 in.; 1 inch = 400 feet (Box 7)
      plan number: IV
    - Zoning map, 1963 March 8; Technical planning Associates; 15 x 13 in.; 1 inch = 400 feet (Box 7)
    - Zoning map, 1963 March 8; Technical planning Associates; 15 x 13 in.; 1 inch = 400 feet (Box 7)
      plan number: VI
    - Zoning map, 1963 March 8; Technical planning Associates; 15 x 13 in.; 1 inch = 400 feet (Box 7)
      plan number: VII